[
    {
        "question": "1. Biased?",
        "answer": "yes"
    },
    {
        "question": "2. Biased?",
        "answer": "yes"
    },
    {
        "question": "3. Representative?",
        "answer": "yes"
    },
    {
        "question": "4. Random?",
        "answer": "yes"
    },
    {
        "question": "5. A number generator has a computer assign each person a number.  Then, it randomly chooses a number, like if we would draw a number out of a bucket.  Random?",
        "answer": "yes"
    },
    {
        "question": "6. What is the population for this question?",
        "answer": "all of the students in the school"
    },
    {
        "question": "7. Is Dahlia's sample a random sample of students in the school?",
        "answer": "no"
    },
    {
        "question": "8. Biased?",
        "answer": "Yes, because they only checked 37 of the 47 ponds."
    },
    {
        "question": "9. Representative?",
        "answer": "No, because her sample has a convenience bias."
    },
    {
        "question": "10. Representative?",
        "answer": "yes"
    },
    {
        "question": "11. Random?",
        "answer": "yes"
    },
    {
        "question": "12. Biased?",
        "answer": "yes"
    },
    {
        "question": "13. Random?",
        "answer": "Yes because they rolled a dice to choose the test number for each person."
    },
    {
        "question": "14. Random?",
        "answer": "yes"
    },
    {
        "question": "15. Random?",
        "answer": "Yes, since the marbles were equal sized, they all had the same chance of falling out."
    },
    {
        "question": "16. What is the population we're talking about here?",
        "answer": "all of the people in the country who pay taxes"
    },
    {
        "question": "17. Is this a random sample?",
        "answer": "Yes, it is.  The millionaires pay taxes too."
    }
]